This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
The White Beard Pirates have successfully pushed into the bay,
but a massive number of Marines still block the path to Ace.
The battle is heating up.
Apologies, Shanks.
But I will not hold back against him.
Hey, I know him! Hawkeye!
I wonder what is written.
Will my hand wipe his name from history?
Or perhaps his fortune shall spare him the fury of this black sword I wield?
The Great Swordsman Mihawk!
Luffy comes under the attack of the Black Sword!
I don't have time to get in a fight with such a strong guy!
All I'm here to do is save Ace!
Go! Second gear!
Yeah!
Yee-haw! Death! Wink!
Galaxy! Wink!
That's it, Straw Boy, well done.
Just keep your eyes on the prize and keep moving forward.
You let us handle the rest.
Don't worry, we'll deal with fancy pants!
Yee-haw!
Yeah!
Hey, Hawkeye!
Remember the time we challenged you?
Well, here comes a blast of the past to kick your smug ass!
We're powered up now as newcomers, and you're gonna feel it!
I don't remember you.
Your worms in a long line of them.
Almost there! Keep running, and don't look back!
Whoa!
What?
You're still... in range.
Whoa!
Yaa-hah!
You're still... in range.
Yaaa-hah!
Yaa-hah!
Oh, man.
He got me.
Only Ace's brother could survive that attack.
Anyone else would have been sliced clean in half.
The turncoat gene bag.
I'm going to make sure that's the last time you so much as touch, Luffy.
Even if it costs me my life.
Why are you doing this?
For one, I don't want to see Ace get murdered.
And I'd like to have a peaceful sea for a change.
It may be too late to avoid the war we've gotten ourselves into now.
But there is still hope.
Namely, in that daring kid over there.
Hope, you say.
We'll see what fate lies in store for him.
But as for you, I'd step back.
Fishman Karate.
Arabesque Brick Fist.
Sharkskin All Frost.
Shark Brick Fist.
That guy's a monster.
He's going in for the kill.
Nobody wants to kill him.
Too close.
He'd have sliced my arms right off if I'd attacked.
So, you're smarter than you look.
Oh, no.
Okay, the sword should not do that.
Could we please call that thing something other than the sword?
He's definitely earned that world's strongest swordsman title.
He's stronger than a mountain of ice.
There's no way Straw Hat's going to survive.
None of he's fighting here.
That's why you don't slice Ice Marks!
Still need footsteps.
No one sees me.
All right, you guys ready?
Time to put Operation Make Captain Buggy look like a badass in front of the world into action.
The Navy loves propaganda, so I'm sure they're broadcasting the war.
We just gotta find us a video transponder snail.
Let's go!
It's shocking how easy it is to encourage them with such vague directions.
So you want to team up?
Nonsense.
Why not?
The reign of these antiquated geriatric pirates like Whitebeard is coming to an end.
He's the last of them.
We're on the brink of a new era, and it belongs to us.
An era where all that matters is the power you yield.
Sounds appealing, right?
You know you want a piece of it.
Oh, come on now.
I can tell that you're intrigued.
Sure, technically you've been stripped of your title, but when you get down to it, we're both warlords at heart, aren't we?
Stop looking at me like you're my equal, cause you're far from it.
If anything, you should be begging to work for me.
Well then, and here I thought you'd been humbled by prison, but not even impelled down could make a dent in you.
Damn straight.
I've heard enough talk.
Sables!
Get lost, you jacko!
I assumed you could be reasoned with, but I was obviously mistaken.
These dumb jawheads don't notice you if you don't try to fight them.
We can just breathe through.
Freeze! Get in the game!
Whoa! He literally got sucked into someone else's might!
Are you gonna move, or do I have to make you? What'll it be?
You're welcome to try, but you will perish before I let you touch my future husband.
Husband?
Yes, my betrothed.
After this ceremony, we'll embark upon an enchanted honeymoon.
Luffy, my love, let us abscond into the depths of amorous euphoria.
But then, what if?
Our bliss has left me famished, my dear.
I'm afraid the food storage is empty, darling.
But the world is full of meals waiting to be cooked.
My darling, cook for me so I can taste your love.
Of course.
Anything for you.
Just give me one moment, darling.
I must be prepared for this possibility.
Luffy's appetite is truly voracious.
If I want to satisfy him, I must be capable of producing a truly colossal feast.
Please make, princess!
We'll be happy to make it for you!
I'll have nothing of it.
Luffy wants to savor the labors of my love, not yours.
Darling, how much longer must I wait?
It's coming, my love.
Such a dying devotion!
I'll gladly embrace any trouble that life throws our way, because it's worth it.
Anything's worth it to be his wife.
His wife!
What the hell?
I can't tell if she wants to fight me or not.
Straw Hat!
Got you!
Are you deaf, you ridiculous fool?
The only way you're getting past me is in a coffin!
Perfume fever!
You're kidding me.
Really?
Stop now!
You'll never make it to your brother in time!
You shall perish after all!
Just freezing through!
Nothing strange here!
There's no denying his fighting skills have improved.
Well, I've already seen all his moves.
There's no chance that I'll miss again.
Not from such a close distance.
Don't find me!
Just passing through!
Come, come!
Yeah!
Oh!
Nice save!
Jet human, chill!
Hey, what's wrong with you?
I'll die!
What?
I didn't slice you!
Besides, I just heard you say,
don't mind me!
I'm here to save you!
There is no way your hearing is that selfishly selective!
Gum gum!
Human shield!
Cut it out!
All right!
Enough!
Your sword's not working!
Suffer the special muggy ball!
And blow off!
Or maybe not.
Do you want to hear a joke instead?
How's the muggy ball like a robust financial market?
I don't know.
How is it?
Say it together, everyone.
Because it goes...
I've never heard that one before!
Nice, Captain Buggy.
Good one!
Thank you, Buggy!
See you in the afterlife, I guess!
We're not done!
Vista, Pop said to make sure Ace's brother doesn't get killed.
Now go!
Back him up!
Certainly!
I shall make haste!
We meet at last.
Your reputation precedes you, Flower Sword Vista.
It's a pleasure to meet you, too!
I'm thrilled you've heard of me!
You can drop the false modesty.
Oh, well, that sucked!
That mustache guy!
Who is he?
I see Straw Hat's true strength.
Well, thanks, whoever you are!
It's nothing to do with physical strength.
His power is to rally those around him.
That's the spirit, Straw Boy!
Keep running!
At least he got past me, Honk.
Muffy!
Save your brother!
You can do it!
Out of my way!
Of all the people seeking to conquer the sea,
he may possess the greatest talent of all.
Ace!
Not again!
That...
That damn straw hat you'll pay for me!
Once again, you've proven how amazing you are!
You let Hawkeye think he'd beaten you,
but in reality, you got exactly what you wanted!
Huh?
What do you mean?
Don't be so coy.
You did it, Captain!
A video transponder snail?
Uh, yeah!
That was definitely my plan.
But did you expect anything less from the man
who's gonna rule the world?
Ha-ha-ha!
I'll follow you to the end of time, Captain Buggy!
Bye!
Shh!
Yeah!
Now, this is where the important part starts.
I wish that the universe would stop encouraging him.
In the looming shadow of Ace's impending execution,
the world has been rocked by one revelation after another.
It all began when more than 200 inmates managed to escape
from the iron-tight prison of Impel Down,
and the most notorious of those prisoners
have now taken a lead role in this epic battle.
The blood-soaked expanse of the ghastly battlefield
is an unearthly sight,
and with a single glance at its horrors,
it's clear that this showdown will change history.
The populace of the world has no choice
but to helplessly observe the events of this war
with the knowledge that its outcome
will determine their very future.
flight admiral, everything has been arranged!
The bay is fully prepared as well.
Yes, sir. We're all set.
What?
They're already preparing for the execution?
Those bastards!
They're pushing up the schedule, are they?
Damn! We don't have much time!
time. Hold on, is it really about to happen? That's ridiculous! Why would they announce the time and
then change it at the last minute? Have to feed. Kill every single video broadcast out of this place.
As representatives of the Navy and the world government, we're fighting to preserve the
righteous cause of absolute justice and we must prevail. Even if that means stepping over the
line. But it's too much for this naive world to understand, let alone see. There's no reason
to submit innocent citizens to the horrific imagery about to unfold. Pops.
Run faster! Damn it, looks like they really are going to execute Ace ahead of time. Ace!
The only news that should spread throughout the world after this war is of our victory,
and the details are irrelevant.
They're attacking our ships!
Look at the bay head! There's something out there!
I'm pretty sure they're not on our side. The Navy must have found a way to get some
reinforcements around the ice wall somehow. But are they admirals? I mean,
these guys are blowing up ships. Shouldn't they be up front?
Is that...?
What... what the hell are they?
Of course, I wondered when I'd get a glimpse of the government's human weapons.
It's that big bear guy! Or I guess I mean guys! There's so many!
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? I'm confused.
A mere hour and a half has passed since the war began, but the Navy aims to end it in one strike.
With this critical push, the tide of the war has once again changed course, flowing into its final stage.
I'm tired of waiting! Let's get this done! Go out there and make me proud!
The Whitebeard Pirates and Navy forces appear to be in a deadlock as powerful fighters from each
side clash again and again. However, when an army of human weapons encircle the battlefield, Luffy and
his allies find themselves overwhelmed by their exclusive attacks. On the next One Piece, the extermination
strategy in action! The power of the pacifistas! I'm gonna be king of the pirates!